

ABOUT ME

I am Fabio Tedesco, graduated in Economics and Business Administration, and I am the manager of a Guest House with 5 rooms. I am interested in the business and IT world. I am a quick learner and capable of managing multiple projects simultaneously thanks to my concurrent work experience during my studies. I consider myself a determined and motivated individual, capable of effective communication and achieving designated objectives.

CONTACTS

PHONE NUMBER: 3385648058

E-MAIL:

Fabio.tedesco1997@gmail.com

FABIO TEDESCO

Born in 04/03/1997 – 26 y/o - Roma

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Guest House Manager – Mary's House – Lido di Ostia 2019 – 2023

NZ Wineries – Blenheim, New Zealand– Vineyard job 10/2018 – 01/2019

Cotto Restaurant – Auckland, New Zealand - Waiter 2018

Tedal & Group – Roma – Labourer – 2017 **Pizzeria Romolo & Luigi** – Lido di Ostia – Waiter 2017

Pizzeria Romolo & Luigi – Lido di Ostia – Delivery pizza 2015-2017

EDUCATION

SAP FI-CO Academy – Accenture – 2023

Università Roma Tre

Bachelor's degree – Economia e gestione aziendale – 2019-2023

Liceo scientifico Scienze Applicate Antonio Labriola Diploma – 2011-2016

SKILLS

- Business accounting
- Software SAP
- Knowledge in Commercial law, labor law and private law
- Knowledge in business and economics
- Knowledge in business organization and business management

Competenze lavorative:

- Budget control
- Sales management
- Team word
- Office suite
- Ability to work under pressure

LINGUE

Italiano – Mother tongue Inglese – Mother tongue